[
    {
        "front": "パソコン",
        "back": "computer",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゲーム",
        "back": "game",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃいん",
        "back": "employee",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほど",
        "back": "about",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶちょう",
        "back": "general manager",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "かちょう",
        "back": "section manager",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうりょう",
        "back": "salary",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "アイディア",
        "back": "idea",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "いっしょうけんめい",
        "back": "as much as one can",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんがえる",
        "back": "to think",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "やくにたつ",
        "back": "to be of use",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃちょう",
        "back": "president",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶちょう",
        "back": "general manager",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "かちょう",
        "back": "section manager",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうりょう",
        "back": "colleague",
        "chapter": "N4 C14"
    }
]
